# **ERIK** SVETLIK

Self-driven full-stack web developer with two years of experience designing, developing, testing and debugging applications within a web-based CMMS using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, ASP, and SQL. Currently earning a certificate in full-stack development from the Web Development Boot Camp at UT Austin, with newly developed skills in React.js, Node.js, MongoDB and MySQL. Passionate about using customer support background to build web applications with high end-user satisfaction, and continuously developing programming knowledge and skills on a personal level.

## CONTACT

svetlik.erik@gmail.com 361.772.1612 linkedin.com/in/erik-svetlik/ github.com/eriksvetlik eriksvetlik.github.io/portfolio

## **SKILLS**

HTML CSS/Bootstrap JavaScript/jQuery ASP SQL VBScript

## **EDUCATION**

### HISTORY B.A.

Aug 2010 - May 2014 Texas A&M University

## **PROJECTS**

Gif-initions
Weather Dashboard
Work Day Scheduler
Halo 5 Missions API
Game of Thrones Quotes API
Nook & Cranny Bookstore
Christmas Countdown
Form Validation

## WORK EXPERIENCE

### ASSISTANT DEVELOPER/CLIENT SUPPORT SPECIALIST AT IMPAK SOLUTIONS

Jan 2020 - Present

Full-Time

In addition to Client Support, I:

- Work in designing, coding, and testing new and current applications alongside the Senior Developer.
- Responsible for daily and weekly backups of software applications and client data using FTP software.
- Was assigned independent programming projects after 2 months of internal training.

#### ■ CLIENT SUPPORT SPECIALIST AT IMPAK SOLUTIONS

Nov 2017 - Dec 2019

Full-Time

- Provided software support and software training to client users.
- Worked with Programming to perform quality assurance tests.
- Managed application requests, project plans and client feedback while providing status updates to clients and management.
- Implemented changes to achieve 91% of service requests completed on time department wide.

## PRODUCT ANALYST AT REYNOLDS AND REYNOLDS

Oct 2015 - Nov 2017

Full-Time

- Assisted in managing and designing leading telephony product.
- Tested programming requests and programming projects for accuracy, optimal functionality, and fulfillment of requests and project goals.
- Wrote program change notices for client and internal users.

# ■ SOFTWARE IMPLEMENTATION CONSULTANT AT REYNOLDS AND REYNOLDS

May 2014 - Oct 2015

Full-Time

- Managed the set-up and training of telephony product.
- Traveled to client sites nationally to work personally with customers.